

HAKAN DAĞLI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

- **Website**
- tr.hakan.dagli@gmail.com
- **** (+90)5075420324
- Ankara
- in /hakandaglinet
- /hakandagli
- M /@tr.hakan.dagli

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering (3,14)

Süleyman Demirel University 2017-2021

Numerical Sciences (80,8)

M. Hakan Güvençer Science High School 2013-2017

OTHER INFOS

Country: Turkey

Date of birth: 29/01/1999 Place of birth: Ankara

Military: Completed (12/2023)

Driving License: B Merital Status: Single

LANGUAGES

English German
Reading B2 Reading A2
Speaking B2 Speaking A1
Writing B2 Writing A1

ABOUT

An experienced Software Engineer with a proven track record in defense industry projects, government initiatives, and e-commerce projects with daily tens of thousands of visitors.

He has been using Angular on the front-end for 3 years. Additionally, he has 16 months of experience with .NET on the back-end.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer (Remote)

NTT DATA Business Solitions Turkey - Japan 01.2023 - Current

Full Stack Developer

ARKSOFT Bilişim - Turkey 10.2021 - 01.2023

Front-End Developer

Akıllı Sınav - Turkey 04.2021-09.2021

SKILLS

Front-End

- ANGULAR
- Spartacus (SAP)
- HTML 5
- CSS 3 / SCSS / SASS
- JavaScript (ES6,ES7)
- TypeScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- PrimeNG

Back-End

.NET CORE

REFERANCES

Mehmet SERT

NTT DATA / FE Team Lead lt.mehmetsert@gmail.com +90 554 995 55 42

Hüsamettin ELALMIŞ

Arksoft Bilişim/Team Lead helalmis@yahoo.com +90 535 560 34 90

Onur SAYGILI (in Germany)

Akıllı Sınav / CTO - Team Lead onursaygili@gmail.com

BLOGS

Javascript asenkron programala ve Event Loop kavramı (Coming Soon)

SAP Commerce Cloud-Spartacus -Angular Ortam Yapılandırması-SSR

<u>Javascript — var-let-const</u> <u>farkları ve scope kavramı</u>

HTML 5'e Giriş

HOBIES

- Football watching/playing
- Off-Road
- Camping
- Reading Literature
- Watching Movies, Series, Documentaries
- Phone and Computer Repairing
- Body Building

PROJECTS

NTT DATA Projects

<u>GRATIS.COM (Front-End)</u>
<u>SpeedyBunny(Front-End)</u> (Kuwait)

ARKSOFT Projects

ARKLICENSE (Full Stack)

EDM (Full Stack)

SESSION AUDIT (Full Stack)

MIP (Front-End)

ARKSSPR (Front-End)

Akıllı Sınav Project

Akıllı Sınav Eğitim Modulü (Front-End)

INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

arksoft.com.tr esinavmerkezi.com yurtoglukalip.com arksspr.com

GITHUB PROJECTS

Video Game Information Site

My Old Personal Website

Arrow Animation App

<u>Okey Taşları</u>

Bidirectional Linked List Animation App

Todo List Drag and Drop (Angular)

Todo List (Js)